Beatriz Strobel

- Wyoming, MI
- **%** (616) 228-5154
- ☑ beatrizstrobel.design@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/beatriz-strobel-50a58a27b
- beatrizstrobelportfolio.onrender.com

Summary

Graphic Designer with 10 years of experience in print publishing, and 1 year of experience in UX design. Excellent typography and image editing skills. Highly experienced in print production. Effective at working in teams in a fast-paced environment. Strong communication skills and project management skills. Attentive to detail, proactive, and creative problem-solver.

EXPERIENCE

FAITH Catholic

Magazine Archive Lead (UX Designer)

Lansing, MI • Remote • 2023 - Current

Assumed the role of Magazine Archive Lead (UX Designer) for FAITH Catholic's digital magazine archive. Oversees features, functionality, and continuous improvement of the web application. Conducts user research, writes user stories and surveys. Designs wireframes and prototypes for the web application on Figma. Conducts usability and accessibility testing and follows WCAG standards.

• Graphic Designer

Lansing, MI • Remote • 2021 - Current

Designs high-quality print magazines in a fast-paced environment. Manages multiple client accounts. Creates digital editions and web images.

Key Accomplishments:

- 2024 ADDY Award: Silver for feature in "Content Evangelist" Fall 2023 (Regional, AAF Lansing).
- 2023 Catholic Media Association Award: 2nd place for Best Special Issue, "The Catholic Miscellany" June 2022.

Right to Life of Michigan Graphic Designer

Grand Rapids, MI • 2016 - 2021

Designed social media graphics, flyers, logos, and benefit dinner invitation packages. Designed and developed a responsive website (self-taught at the time) using HTML, CSS, and Google Maps API. Collaborated on-site with a professional photographer and local charities in Detroit to create content for helpinthed.org.

SKILLS

Graphic Design

- · Adobe Creative Suite
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- After Effects

UX

- Figma
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- User Research
- Usability Testing
- Information
 Architecture

Web Development

- HTML
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- · React.js
- Apollo GraphQL
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Node.js
- Agile Development
- Git Version Control

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design

University of Michigan Ann Arbor, MI

Full Stack Web Development Certificate Michigan State University Lansing, MI